Guide to the Daniel A. Livingstone Papers, 1950-2001 UA.29.02.0253
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Daniel Livingstone Papers
1950-2001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Livingstone, Daniel A.
UA.29.02.0253
36 Linear Feet
Daniel A. Livingstone is the James B. Duke Professor Emeritus of Biology at Duke University, with longstanding research interests in biology, limnology, paleolimnology, zoology, and other subjects. The Daniel A. Livingstone papers include the extensive correspondence of Dr. Livingstone from the 1980s to 2001 as well as other materials related to his research and teaching at Duke University.
Collection Overview
The Daniel A. Livinstone papers consist primarily of the extensive correspondence of Daniel Livingstone with scientists and colleagues related to his research interests in biology, limnology, paleolimnology, and other subjects. Other materials are related to his work on a variety of research grants, classes taught at Duke University, and other topics.
This collection has not yet been processed.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection has not yet been processed. Unprocessed materials may require additional time before access can be granted.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their education records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Records, such as search committee files or others pertaining to employment where individuals are identified, are closed for 70 years.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Biographical Note
Daniel A. Livingstone was born August 3, 1927 in Detroit, Michigan. He attended Dalhousie University in Nova Scotia, Canada, graduating with a Bachelor's of Science in 1948 and a Masters of Science in 1950. He then pursued a PhD at Yale University, finishing in 1953. He taught ecology, limnology, zoology, biology, and geology courses at Duke and was the James B. Duke Professor Emeritus of Biology. In 1989, he was awarded the G. Evelyn Hutchinson Award by the American Society of Limnology and Oceanography for his research in Africa and North America in the areas of limnology, paleolimnology, and paleoecology.
Livingstone's research interests were primarily in bioclimatology, limnology, and paleolimnology, but he also published work on a wide variety of subjects including zoology, paleontology, fish populations and zoogeography, coring technologies, and pollen analysis. He was also the inventor of a corer, named the Livingstone corer, used by many American palynologists and paleolimnologists. He conducted extensive research in sub-Saharan Africa, including Cameroon, Kenya, Ghana, amd Tanzania, as well as in North America, particularly Nova Scotia. He was also awarded numerous grants from the National Science Foundation and other organizations, and corresponded with many professionals in the fields of biology, limnology, paleolimnology, ecology, climatology, and many other areas.
Daniel Livingstone married Dr. Pat Palmer, a botanist and professor, in 1989. He died March 6, 2016 in Raleigh, North Carolina.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Daniel A. Livingstone papers were received by the University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2015.
Limnology; Paleolimnology -- Quarternary; Climatic changes; Kenya; Cameroon; Livingstone, Daniel A.; Duke University. Department of Biology.; Duke University -- Faculty
- Correspondence, 1
  - Misc Correspondence (Box 9)
  - African letters (Box 9)
  - Cameroon (correspondence) (Box 9)
  - unlabeled folders of correspondence (Box 9)
  - "Prof. stuff to do soon" (contains correspondence) (Box 9)
  - Abell, Dr. Paul I. (Box 13)
  - Abonu people, 1999 (Box 13)
  - Abonu (Box 13)
  - Andrew, Adam (Box 13)
  - Adamson, Donald (Box 13)
  - African Archaelogical Review (Box 13)
  - Ager, Thomas (Box 13)
  - Agwu, Charles (Box 13)
  - Akomeah, James (Box 13)
  - Allanson, BR (Box 13)
  - Ambrose, Stanley (Box 13)
  - American Scientist (Box 13)
  - Amoah, Cecilia (Box 13)
  - AMOCO (Box 13)
  - Amqua (American Quaternary Association) (Box 13)
  - Anderson, Pat (Box 13)
  - Anderson, Elizabeth (Box 13)
  - Andrews, John (Box 13)
  - Angyal, Jennifer (Box 13)
  - Annual Reviews (Box 13)
  - APD (Box 13)
  - ASLO (Box 13)
  - Assoc. des Palynologues de langue francaise (Box 13)
  - Augustine, David (Box 13)
  - Ayensu, Edward S. (Box 13)
  - A Misc. (current year) (Box 13)
  - A Misc., 1996 (Box 13)
  - A Misc., 1991-1995 (Box 13)
  - A Misc., 1986-1990 (Box 13)
  - A Misc., 1981-1985 (Box 13)
  - Bada, Jeffrey (Box 13)
  - Baikal Workshop (Box 13)
  - Baker, Brian H. (Box 13)
  - Banta, Gary (Box 13)
  - Barnett. Raymond J. (Box 13)
  - Barnett, Ray meeting, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Barton, Dr. Charles E. (Box 13)
  - Barotn, Charles E. (Box 13)
  - Baruch, Uri (Box 13)
  - Beadle, Leonard (Box 13)
  - Bean, A. K. (Box 13)
  - Beasley, John (Box 13)
  - Beaulieu, JL. De (Box 13)
  - Bedford job file (Box 13)
  - Benson, Larry (Box 13)
  - Benson, Larry (Box 13)
  - Benson cont. (Box 13)
  - Bernabo, J. Christopher (Box 13)
  - Bikemu, G. (Box 14)
  - Billings, W. D. (Box 14)
  - Bilson, John (Box 14)
  - Binford, Michael (Box 14)
  - Bliley, Dan (Box 14)
  - Blomquist, Sven (Box 14)
  - Blum, Michael (Box 14)
  - Blum and G.S. (Box 14)
  - Blum (Box 14)
  - unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - Blum, Michael (Box 14)
  - Blumenchine, Robt. J. (Box 14)
  - Boaz, N. T. (Box 14)
  - Bodick, Peggy (Box 14)
  - Boltonhagen, E. (Box 14)
  - Bonnefille, Dr. Ramonde (Box 14)
  - Bonnefille, R. (Box 14)
  - Bonnefille, Raymonde: Elmenteita Counting Sheets, Jan. 27, 1979 (Box 14)
  - Bornbusch, Alan (Box 14)
  - Bower, John (Box 14)
  - Bowser, Carl (Box 14)
  - Bradley, Dr. Wh. H. (Box 14)
  - Bradley, W.H. (Box 14)
  - Brandt, Steven (Box 14)
  - Gail A. Brooks (Box 14)
  - Brosset, A. (Box 14)
  - Dr. Lewis Brown (Box 14)
  - Linda Brubaker (Box 14)
  - Grace Brush (Box 14)
  - Bryan, Kirk Jr. (Box 14)
  - Bryson, Reid (Box 14)
  - Bryson, Reid A. (Box 14)
  - Burgess Letters, attributed to Dr. Mary Burgess (Box 14)
  - Burney, David, 1986- (Box 14)
  - unlabeled folder [Burney, David?] (Box 14)
  - Burney, 1984-1985 (Box 14)
  - unlabeled folder (Box 14)
  - Burney, David, 1982-1983 (Box 14)
  - Lida P. Burney (Box 14)
  - Bush, Mark (Box 14)
  - Karl Butzer (Box 14)
  - B Misc. (current year) (Box 14)
  - B Misc., 1996 (Box 14)
  - B Misc., 1991-1995 (Box 14)
  - B Misc., 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - B Misc., 1984-1985 (Box 15)
  - B Misc., -1983 (Box 15)
  - Cahoon, Larry (Box 15)
  - Callaway, J. Lamar (Box 15)
  - Cambridge University Press (Box 15)
  - Cameroun (Box 15)
  - Madagascar sites (Box 15)
  - C-14 Malawi (Box 15)
  - C-14 Nags Head NC USA (Box 15)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 15)
  - C-14 Rukwa Tanzania (Box 15)
  - Small Momela, Mt. Meru, Tanzania (Box 15)
  - Cameroun General Info (Box 15)
  - Cameroun notes, misc. (Box 15)
  - Cameroun next trip (Box 15)
  - Cameroun letters, visa, etc. (Box 15)
  - Cameroun 1985 packing list and shipping (Box 15)
  - Cameroun 1985 packing list and shipping: shipping (Box 15)
  - Cameroun 1985 packing list and shipping: air frieght (Box 15)
  - Cameroun research permit, duty free entry police report, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Canqua (Box 15)
  - Carlquist, Sherwin (Box 15)
  - Carney, Heath (Box 15)
  - Carpenter, Steve (Box 15)
  - Cassanova, Joel (see also Anne-Marie Lezine (Box 15)
  - Alene Nordstrom Case (see also Ogden, J. G. (Pete)) (Box 15)
  - James M. Case (Mike) External Exam, Dalhousie (Box 15)
  - Thure, Cerling (Box 15)
  - Victor Chain (Box 15)
  - Colin Chapman (Box 15)
  - John J. Chapman (Box 15)
  - Chapman misc. (Box 15)
  - Chapman, Lauren and Colin (Box 15)
  - Chen, Yinshuo (Box 15)
  - Clark, J. D. (Box 15)
  - Ms. For Causes and Consequences of Food Production in Africa, J. Desmond Clark and Steven Brandt, eds.: "Interactions of Food Production and Changing Vegetation in Africa", October 1, 1979 (Box 15)
  - Clark, J.D. (Box 15)
  - Jim Clark (Box 15)
  - Jim Clark file (Box 15)
  - Clayton, Derek (Box 15)
  - Coe, Malcolm (Box 15)
  - Coetzee, J. A. (Box 15)
  - Cohen, Andrew (Box 15)
  - Cohen, David W. (Box 15)
  - Paul Colinvaux, 1997 (Box 16)
  - Paul Colinvaux, 1990-1996 (Box 16)
  - Paul Colinvaux, 1985-1989 (Box 16)
  - Paul Colinvaux, 1980-1984 (Box 16)
  - Paul Colinvaux, 1970-1079 (Box 16)
  - Colton, Tom (Box 16)
  - Collegiate Academy: Mars Hill College (Box 16)
  - Ed Connor (Box 16)
  - Cooke, H. B. S. (Box 16)
  - Cooper, Arthur W. (Box 16)
  - Ives Coppens (Box 16)
  - Michael Corcoran (Box 16)
  - Corliss, Bruce (Box 16)
  - Coulter, G. W. (Box 16)
  - Covich, Alan (Box 16)
  - Crater Lakes (Box 16)
  - Career, Ken (Box 16)
  - Crisman, Thomas L. (Box 16)
  - Cross, Scott (Box 16)
  - Crossley, Robert (Box 16)
  - Crow, Michael (Box 16)
  - Crow, Michael J. (Box 16)
  - Cushing, Edward J. (Box 16)
  - Cushing, Edward J. (Box 16)
  - Cwynar, Leslie (Box 16)
  - C-Misc Current Year- (Box 16)
  - C-Misc 96- (Box 16)
  - C-Misc 91-95 (Box 16)
  - C-Misc 86-90 (Box 16)
  - C-Misc 81-85 (Box 16)
  - Darling, Marilyn Stagner (Box 16)
  - C14 Dating: Forms and Instructions Beta (Box 16)
  - C14 Dating: Isotrace Labs (Box 16)
  - C14 Dating: Old Forms and Instructions (Box 16)
  - C14 Dating: Lari Swamp, Kenya (Box 16)
  - David, Nicholas (Box 16)
  - Davis, David (Box 16)
  - Davis, Frank (Box 16)
  - Davis, Margie Bryan (Box 16)
  - Davis, Ronald B. (Box 16)
  - Dean, Richard (Box 16)
  - DeBusk, George Henry Jr. 95- (Box 16)
  - DeBusk, George Henry Jr. 94- (Box 16)
  - DeBusk, George Henry Jr., working papers (Box 17)
  - DeDeckker, Dr. (Australia) (Box 17)
  - Deelstra, H. (empty) (Box 17)
  - Deevy, E.S. Jr.: Festschrift (Box 17)
  - Deevy, E.S. Jr.: Obituary (Box 17)
  - Deevy, E.S. Jr: Obituary Notes (Box 17)
  - Deevy, E.S. Jr. (Box 17)
  - Degens, Egon T. (Box 17)
  - DeGraw, Martin: Zoology 191-192.62 T (Box 17)
  - Dey, George Jerry Sefa (Box 17)
  - Delcourt, Paul and Hazel (Box 17)
  - Delpierre, X (Box 17)
  - Dickman, Mike (Box 17)
  - Dmetriev, George (empty) (Box 17)
  - Dobbs, Fred (Box 17)
  - Dominey, Wallace (Box 17)
  - Donner, Joachin (Box 17)
  - Dow Corning (Box 17)
  - Douglas, Marianne (Box 17)
  - Doyle, Roger (Box 17)
  - Driscoll, A.H (Box 17)
  - Duke Safety (Box 17)
  - Duke University Officials (Box 17)
  - Duke University Research Council (Box 17)
  - DURC Travel to Meetings 1990: Baikal Workshop, Charleston 10/21-24/90 (Box 17)
  - DURC Travel to Meetings 1989: DURC and Private Expense Europe August-Sept. 1989 (Box 17)
  - DURC Travel to Meetings 1989: Personal Expenses, NS and Alaska (Box 17)
  - DURC Travel to Meetings Pre-1989: (Box 17)
  - DURC Travel to Meetings Pre-1989: J. Desmond Clark Conference Travel (Box 17)
  - Duke University Misc: Med Photo/ Audiovisual Educ. (Box 17)
  - Duke University- Miscellanous (Box 17)
  - Dr. H. Dumont (Box 17)
  - Dunseath, Wm. J. Ross Jr. (Box 17)
  - Durand, Mark (Box 17)
  - D-Misc. - Current (Box 17)
  - D-Misc.- '96 (Box 17)
  - D-Misc.- '91-95 (Box 17)
  - D-Misc.- '86-90 (Box 17)
  - D-Misc.- Outdated (-'85) (Box 17)
  - East African Freshwater Fisheries Research Organization (EAFFRO) (Box 17)
  - Ebinger, Cynthia (Box 17)
  - Eccles, David (Box 17)
  - Ecological Society of America (Box 17)
  - Edmund, John (Box 17)
  - Edmundson, W.T (Box 17)
  - Edmundson, Yvette: (Limnol. Oceanogr.) '84- (Box 17)
  - Edmundson, Yvette: (Limnol. Oceanogr.)'77-'83 (Box 17)
  - Edmundson, Yvette: (Limnol. Oceanogr.) '80-94 (Box 17)
  - Edmundson, Yvette: (Limnol. Oceanogr.)'75-'76 (Box 17)
  - Emliani, C: Ice Age (Box 17)
  - Episodes (Box 17)
  - Erdtman, Gunnar (Box 17)
  - Eugster, Hans (Box 17)
  - Eugster, Hans (Box 17)
  - E-Misc- '96- (Box 17)
  - E-Misc-'91-'95 (Box 17)
  - E-Misc-'86-'90 (Box 17)
  - E-Misc-'85 (Box 17)
  - Eylers, John (Box 17)
  - Faegry, Knut (Box 18)
  - Fairbridge, Rhodes W. (Box 18)
  - Fafr, Jacob (Box 18)
  - Farris, Fred (Box 18)
  - Faure, Huguges (Box 18)
  - Fetterman, Bruce (Box 18)
  - Field, Tremayne (Box 18)
  - Fieldhouse, William (Box 18)
  - Finkl, Charles W. (Box 18)
  - Fleischer, Michael (Box 18)
  - Flenley, JR (Box 18)
  - Flint, R.F. (Empty) (Box 18)
  - Flora, Mark (Box 18)
  - Ford, S.O (Box 18)
  - Frank, Peter (Box 18)
  - Fraser, Heidi:GS Application 1990-1999 (Box 18)
  - French, Bevan M. (Box 18)
  - Frey, Dave G. (Box 18)
  - Fritz, Cherilyn C. (Box 18)
  - Frost, Ian (Box 18)
  - Frothingham, Thomas E. (Malaria, Other Medical Info) (Box 18)
  - Fuller, Manley (Box 18)
  - Fulton, Roland S. III (Box 18)
  - F Misc- '96- (Box 18)
  - F. Misc.-'91-'95 (Box 18)
  - F. Misc.-'86-'90 (Box 18)
  - Garrels, Robert M. (Box 18)
  - Gasse, Francoise (Box 18)
  - Gaudet, John (Box 18)
  - Gensel, Patricia (Box 18)
  - Gentry, Al (Box 18)
  - Geologie Du Quaternaire (Box 18)
  - Ghana Embassey (Box 18)
  - Gilbert, Barrie (Box 18)
  - Gilbert, Robert (Box 18)
  - Gilhen, John NSMS (Box 18)
  - Gillett, J.B. (Box 18)
  - Godwin, Harry (Empty) (Box 18)
  - Chretien Goetz (Box 18)
  - Goldman, Charles G. (Box 18)
  - Goman, Michelle (Box 18)
  - Gorham, E. (Box 18)
  - Graduate Student Applicants 1984 (Box 18)
  - Graduate Student Applicants 1982 (Box 18)
    Scope and Contents
    RESTRICTED
  - Graduate Student Applicants 1979,1980 (Box 18)
  - Graduate Student Applicants 1978 (Box 18)
  - Graduate Student Applicants 1976 (Box 18)
  - Graebner, Steven (Box 18)
  - Graebner, Laurie Jane (Box 18)
  - Graham, Allan (Box 18)
  - Grant, Douglas (Box 18)
  - Graybeal, Beth (Box 18)
  - Grayson, John and Marie (Box 18)
  - Gregg, John (Box 18)
  - Green, James (Box 18)
  - Greenidge, K. N. H. (Box 18)
  - Greenwood, P.H (Box 18)
  - Grimm, Eric (Box 18)
  - Grove, A.T. (Box 18)
  - Grove, Matt (Box 18)
  - Grzybowski, Krysztof (Box 18)
  - Guinet (Van Campo: CNRS, Montpellier (Box 18)
  - G-Misc- Current Year (Box 19)
  - G-Misc-'91- (Box 19)
  - G-Misc-'85 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1997- (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1992-1996 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Haberyan, Kurt, 1983 (Box 19)
  - Haff, Peter (Box 19)
  - Halfman, John (Box 19)
  - Hall, John/Theresa (Box 19)
  - Hamilton, Alan (Box 19)
  - Hammond, Tom Van Der (Box 19)
  - Harvey, Paul (Box 19)
  - Harvey, Thomas J. (Box 19)
  - Haas, Peter (Box 19)
  - Hay, Richard L. (Box 19)
  - Hayden, James (Box 19)
  - Hayes, Jennifer (Box 19)
  - Hayes, F. Ronald (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Carol (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Robert: DATA-Ms-Proposals (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Carol (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Robert E. Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Robert E. Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Dr. Robert: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
  - Hecky, Robert E.: Data, CV, Recommendation (Box 19)
  - Hedges, R. E. M. (Box 19)
  - Francis Henderson (Box 19)
  - Herbarium (Box 19)
  - Herbarium Misc. (Box 19)
  - US National Herbarium (Box 19)
  - Belgian National Herbarium (Box 19)
  - East African Herbarium (Box 20)
  - Hertz Rent-a-car (Box 20)
  - Dr. Gregory F. Herzog (Box 20)
  - C.J. Heusser (Box 20)
  - Hevly, Richard (Box 20)
  - Hijman, Maria E.E. (Box 20)
  - Claude Hillaire-Marcel (Box 20)
  - Hines, Debbie (Box 20)
  - Dian Hitchcock (Box 20)
  - Hickson, Connie Thetford (Box 20)
  - John Hobbie (Box 20)
  - Stephen Holdship (Box 20)
  - Robert Holmes (Box 20)
  - Jeffrey Geo Hope (Box 20)
  - David Hopkins (Box 20)
  - Horie, Shoji (Box 20)
  - Horie, S. (Box 20)
  - Hove, A. R. T. (Box 20)
  - Hu, Feng Sheng (Box 20)
  - Hubbs, Carl L. (Box 20)
  - Hull, Celli (Box 20)
  - Hull, James (Box 20)
  - Hutchison, Beth (Box 20)
  - G. E. Hutchinson (Box 20)
  - M. Hyder (Box 20)
  - H Misc., Current year (Box 20)
  - H Misc., 1996 (Box 20)
  - H Misc., 1991-1995 (Box 20)
  - H Misc., 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - H Misc., 1985 (Box 20)
  - Ibe, Ralph A. (Box 20)
  - ICSEB Symposia (Box 20)
  - Inqua: IGCP Project No. 146: River flood and lake level changes (Box 20)
    Project leaders: Roland Paepe and Leon De Meyer
  - Imamba, S. K. (Box 20)
  - Imbrie, John (Box 20)
  - Inqua (Box 20)
  - Inskep, Ray (Box 20)
  - International Biological Program (Box 20)
  - Isaac, Glen (Box 20)
  - Dr. Glen Isaac (Box 20)
  - I Misc., Current year (Box 20)
  - I Misc., outdated (Box 20)
  - Jacobs, Bonnie Fine (Box 20)
  - Susan Jacobson (Box 20)
  - Danny Jenson (Box 20)
  - JGR (Box 20)
  - JGR MSS (Box 20)
  - JGR (Box 20)
  - Don Johnson (Box 20)
  - Tom Johnson, 1993 (Box 20)
  - Tom Johnson, 1991-1992 (Box 20)
  - Tom Johnson, 1984-1990 (Box 21)
  - Tom Johnson, 1983 (Box 21)
  - Jones, Blair (Box 21)
  - Lois Jones (Box 21)
  - Susan G. Jones: Position Classification Request (Box 21)
  - Susan G. Jones (Box 21)
  - William Jones (Box 21)
  - JOPH (Box 21)
  - Journal of Paleolimnology (Box 21)
  - Anne Juliett (Box 21)
  - Adrian Juncosa (Box 21)
  - Juwayeyi, Y. M. (Box 21)
  - J Misc., Current year (Box 21)
  - J Misc., 1991 (Box 21)
  - J Misc., outdated, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Kaczmarska, Irene (Box 21)
  - Kamau, Celia (Box 21)
  - Kat, Peter W. (Box 21)
  - Kaufman, Les (Box 21)
  - Kaufman, Peter B. (Box 21)
  - Kay, Richard F. (Box 21)
  - Kelly, Wanda (Box 21)
  - Keltz, Kerry (Box 21)
  - Keltz, Dr. Kerry R. (Box 21)
  - K. Keltz Seisemographs (Box 21)
  - Kendall, Robert L. (Box 21)
  - Kendall, Robert, 1974- (Box 21)
  - G.O. Kesse Geological Survey of ACCRA (Box 21)
  - G.O. Kesse (unlabled) (Box 21)
  - Kidd, Terra (Box 21)
  - Kilham, Peter, 1987-90 (Box 21)
  - Kilham, Peter, 1983-86 (Box 21)
  - Kilham, Peter, 1978-82 (Box 21)
  - Kilham, Peter, 1973-1977 (Box 21)
  - Peter Kilham Budget and Plans (Box 21)
  - Kilham, Susan Correspondence (Box 21)
  - Kilhams: Diatom MS (Box 21)
  - King, Carolyn (Box 21)
  - King, Carolyn (Box 21)
  - Kinsolver, Joel (Box 21)
  - Kjellmarc, Eric (Box 21)
  - Klein, Melanie (Box 21)
  - Klein, Richard G. (Box 21)
  - Kling, George, 1993- (Box 22)
  - Kling, George, 1990-1992 (Box 22)
  - Kling, George, 1988-1989 (Box 22)
  - Kling, George, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Kling, George, 1985- (Box 22)
  - Kling, George Dissertation (Box 22)
  - Kramer, Amy (Box 22)
  - Kress, John (Box 22)
  - Krishnamuhtry, R.V (Box 22)
  - Krot, Michael (Box 22)
  - Kutzbach, John (Box 22)
  - Kyauka, Pelaji S. (Box 22)
  - Kwaw, Gloria (Box 22)
  - K-Misc-Current year 96 (Box 22)
  - K-Misc 91-95 (Box 22)
  - K-Misc 86-90 (Box 22)
  - K-Misc Outdated '85 (Box 22)
  - Labouriau, Maria (Box 22)
  - Labarbera, Mike (Box 22)
  - Lack, Andrew (Box 22)
  - Lajtha, Kate (Box 22)
  - Lake Rudolph (Box 22)
  - Lake Victoria (Box 22)
  - Laseski, Ruth (Box 22)
  - Leakey Foundation (Box 22)
  - Leakey, Dr. Richard (Box 22)
  - Leavitt, Peter R (Box 22)
  - Lees, Cynthia (Box 22)
  - Leff, David (Box 22)
  - LeFournier, Dr. Jacques (Box 22)
  - Leitz, E (Box 22)
  - Lenk, Cecilia (Box 22)
  - Leopold, Estella (Box 22)
  - Levesque, Christine M. (Box 22)
  - Lewis, William M. Jr. (Box 22)
  - Lezine, Anne-Marie (Box 22)
  - L (Box 22)
  - Liminology Oceanography (Box 22)
  - Limnological Society of Southern Africa (Box 22)
  - Lindeburg, Staffan (Box 22)
  - Lindeke, Marjorie I (Box 22)
  - Liu, Jianjun (Box 22)
  - Wock, Michael (Box 22)
  - Loffler, Heinz (Box 22)
  - Londer, Randi (Box 22)
  - Longman's Inc (Box 22)
  - Lubell, David (Box 22)
  - Luck, Anne E. (Secretary), May 28, 1980 - July 31, 1981 (Box 22)
  - Ludlam, Stuart (Box 22)
  - Lynch, Jason (Box 22)
  - L-Misc. Current Year '96 (Box 23)
  - L-Misc. '90-'95 (Box 23)
  - L-Misc. '85-'89 (Box 23)
  - L-Misc. '80-'84 (Box 23)
  - Macintire, Sally (Box 23)
  - Macintire, Sally, 1989- (Box 23)
  - Macintire, Sally, 1981-1988 (Box 23)
  - Macintire, Sally, -1980 (Box 23)
  - Macintire, Sally, 1975 (Box 23)
  - Maglione, Gilbert F. (Box 23)
  - Environmental Magnetism Newsletter (Box 23)
  - Mahaney, W.C. (Box 23)
  - Maher, Louis (Box 23)
  - Mahoney, Sheila (Box 23)
  - Maitima, Joseph (Box 23)
  - Mworia-Maitima, Joseph (Box 23)
  - Mworia-Maitima, Joseph, 1989- (Box 23)
  - Maitima, Joseph, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Maitima, Joseph, 1982-87 (Box 23)
  - Malely, J. (Volcan MS) (Box 23)
  - Malely, Jean (Box 23)
  - Maley, J, 1986 (Box 23)
  - Maley, J, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Maley, J, 1984 (Box 23)
  - Maley, J, 1983 (Box 24)
  - Maley, J, 1982 (Box 24)
  - Maley, J Housing Search (Box 24)
  - Maley, J, 1980-1981 (Box 24)
  - Maley, J, -1979 (Box 24)
  - Manabe, Syukuro (Box 24)
  - Mann, Mike (Box 24)
  - Mantuani, Mark A. (Box 24)
  - Maps (Box 24)
  - Martin, Lynn (Box 24)
  - Martin, Paul (Box 24)
  - Mathai, Stephen (Box 24)
  - Masao, Fidel T. (Box 24)
  - Matthews, Charlie M. (Box 24)
  - Maunsell, John (Box 24)
  - Mvuti, Ken (Box 24)
  - Sarah May (Box 24)
  - McAndrews, John H. (Box 24)
  - McAndrews, Jack H. (John) (Box 24)
  - McBrearty, Sally (Box 24)
  - McCafferty, Keith (Box 24)
  - Tim McClanahan Ms (Box 24)
  - Tim McClanahan (Box 24)
  - Gene McDonold (Box 24)
  - McDonald Travel Incorporated: Gale Davis, formerly of World Travel Agency (Box 24)
  - Michael McFarland (Box 24)
  - McGraw-Hill Goldman's Limnology book: D.A.L. review (Box 24)
  - McGraw-Hill book company (Box 24)
  - McHaro, Tumaini (Box 24)
  - McIntosh, Roderick (Box 24)
  - McKaye, Kenneth R. (Box 24)
  - McKenna, James (Box 24)
  - Mdala, Chisengu (Box 24)
  - Meadows, M. E. (Box 24)
  - Megard, Robert O. (Box 24)
  - Mehringer, Peter J. (Box 24)
  - Meier, Mary Pat (Box 24)
  - Melack, John, 1986 (Box 24)
  - Melack, John, 1977-1985 (Box 24)
  - Melack, John, 1976 (Box 24)
  - Melack, John, 1975 (Box 24)
  - Melack, Mike (Box 24)
  - Mellon Foundation (Box 24)
  - Menell, Roger P. N. (Box 24)
  - Meybeck, Michael (Box 24)
  - Meyers, Philip A. (Box 24)
  - K. Miller Beuning, 1997 (Box 24)
  - Beuning Ms (Box 24)
  - Kristina R. Miller (Box 24)
  - Norton Miller (Box 24)
  - Elizabeth Mills (Box 24)
  - Mills, J. A. (Box 24)
  - Katherine Mills (Box 24)
  - Mitchell, Frank (Box 25)
  - Money, Nicholas (Zambia) (Box 25)
  - Monroe, Alice (Box 25)
  - Moran, Nancy and Linda (Box 25)
  - Moore, Allen M. (Box 25)
  - Morgan, A.V. (Box 25)
  - Morgan, Dr. Paul I. (Box 25)
  - Morgan, Robert (Box 25)
  - Morin, Peter (Box 25)
  - Morin, Sarah J. (Box 25)
  - Morrison, Mabel (Box 25)
  - Mortimer, C.H. (Box 25)
  - Motten, Alec (Box 25)
  - Mountain Club of Uganda (Box 25)
  - Tom Mowbray (Box 25)
  - Msaky, Emma (Box 25)
  - Muller, German (Box 25)
  - Murdoch, Barbara (Box 25)
  - M. Misc., Current year (Box 25)
  - M. Misc., -1996 (Box 25)
  - M. Misc., 1991-1995 (Box 25)
  - M. Misc., 1986-1990 (Box 25)
  - M. Misc., 1985 (Box 25)
  - Nag, Gabriel (Cameroun) (Box 25)
  - NASA (Box 25)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 25)
  - National Geographic Society (Box 25)
  - National Institute of the Environment (Box 25)
  - National Research Council (Box 25)
  - New England Aquarium (Box 25)
  - Nijhout, H. F. (Box 25)
  - NOAA Proposals to review (Box 25)
  - Nova Scotia Museum Natural History (Box 25)
  - National Science Foundation General Correspondence, Current year (Box 25)